<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<panel
follows="all"
height="600"
layout="topleft"
left="0"
name="panel_login"
focus_root="false" 
top="600"
 width="996">
<panel.string name="create_account_url">
       http://join.secondlife.com/
</panel.string>
<string name="reg_in_client_url" translate="false">
     http://secondlife.eniac15.lindenlab.com/reg-in-client/
</string>
<panel.string name="forgot_password_url">
       http://secondlife.com/account/request.php
</panel.string>
  <web_browser
  visibility_control="ExperimentalLogin"
  tab_stop="false" 
  trusted_content="true" 
  bg_opaque_color="Black"
  border_visible="false"
  top="-600"
  follows="all"
  start_url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/53euICErnVg?autoplay=1&amp;loop=1&amp;playlist=53euICErnVg"
  left="0"
  name="html"
  height="650"
  width="996" />
  
  <!--<icon
  follows="all"
  height="600"
  image_name="Login_BG"
  color="1 1 1 1"
  layout="topleft"
  name="login_bg"
  mouse_opaque="false"
  visible="true"
  width="1016"
  left="0"
  top="-600"/>-->
  <icon
  follows="bottom|left|right"
  height="125"
  image_name="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
  color="0.15 0.05 0 1"
  layout="topleft"
  name="login_bg"
  mouse_opaque="false"
  visible="true"
  width="996"
  left="0"
  top="-125"/>
  <icon
  follows="bottom|left|right"
  height="125"
  image_name="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
  color="0 0 0 1"
  layout="topleft"
  name="login_bg"
  mouse_opaque="false"
  visible="true"
  width="996"
  left="0"
  top="-125"/>
  
  <icon
  follows="top|left|right"
  height="20"
  image_name="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
  color="0 0 0 1"
  layout="topleft"
  name="login_bg"
  mouse_opaque="false"
  visible="true"
  width="996"
  left="0"
  top="0"/>
  <icon
  follows="top|left|right"
  height="20"
  image_name="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
  color="0.15 0.05 0 1"
  layout="topleft"
  name="login_bg"
  mouse_opaque="false"
  visible="true"
  width="996"
  left="0"
  top="0"/>
  <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left|right"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top="20"
    width="994"/>
  <button
       follows="left|top|right"
       height="20"
       image_unselected="transparentj2c"
       image_selected="transparentj2c"
       label="[CHANNEL] [VERSION] - [2.6.2 - Ending Dragon]"
       font="SansSerifSmall"
       layout="topleft"
       left="3"
       halign="left"
       name="channel_text"
       top="1"
       width="994">
       <button.commit_callback
         function="Floater.Show"
         parameter="sl_about"/>
       </button>
  <layout_stack
    border_size="0"
    follows="all"
    height="445"
    layout="topleft"
    left="0"
    mouse_opaque="false"
    name="root_stack"
    orientation="vertical"
    top="20"
    width="998">
      <layout_panel
      auto_resize="true"
      visibility_control="ShowChangelogs"
      follows="all"
      height="490"
      layout="topleft"
      mouse_opaque="false"
      name="info_panel"
      top_pad="0"
      width="998">
       <scroll_container
       color="Transparent"
       follows="all"
       layout="topleft"
       mouse_opaque="false"
       left="0"
       name="camera_scroll"
       opaque="true"
       height="487"
       width="994"
       top="3">
       <panel
       follows="all"
       height="2073"
       layout="topleft"
       left="0"
       name="panel_login2"
       top="0"
       width="980">
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="313"
              top="10"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Checkbox to control weither a projector should cast a shadow or not. (LOCAL)
Added: Distance display to "Nearby" people panel.
Added: Loadingscreen tip for the Email verification.
Added: Cinematic Camera option to camera preferences tab.
Added: Scene Memory info to about floater.
Changed: Properly carry over the shader success signal when toggling shaders.
Changed: Improved SSAO defaults even further.
Changed: Improved some loadingscreen tips.
Changed: Improved scaling of text field widgets, fixes slider text fields having a slightly darker color at the bottom.
Changed: Improved SSR looks a bit.
Changed: Object Quality "Very High" to 7.5 and "Ultra" to 10.
Changed: Inventory filter being to big.
Changed: Version to 2.6.2.
Fixed: Warnings in panel_places.xml.
Fixed: Compile.
Fixed: Floater Script Limits floater warnings and new size.
Fixed: German translation for the cycle link/face menu entries.
Fixed: Inventory inbox background not big enough.
Fixed: German translation in about floater containing weird symbols.
Fixed: Inventory inbox layout clipping.
Removed: Non-functional Normalmap Scale option from preferences.
Removed: Unused Blocked List menu entry.
Misc: Cleanup.
Merge with Release. (215 changes)
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.6.1
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="285"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Ability to change the cloud noise texture in edit sky floater, without restart this time around.
Added: Cloud Noise Maps from Nirans Viewer, tweaked the High Resolution one to be smaller.
Added: Loadingscreen tip system.
Added: 22 completely new tips, shorter and more helpful than before.
Added: Another cloud noise map.
Added: Downloading Update loadingscreen text. (Untested)
Changed: Most if not all notifications links about downloads and viewer versions to my own links.
Changed: Tweaks to SSAO smoothing.
Changed: Tweaked IM floater chat bar positioning and size, long overdue.
Changed: Loadingscreen layout.
Changed: Initial startup loading percentages.
Changed: Increased wearables wait timeout to lessen cases in which you are falsely presented with the choose sex dialog.
Changed: Allow parsing icons in chat, history and picks again.
Changed: Version to 2.6.1
Changed: Disabled showing Release Notes on first start on a new version.
Fixed: Shadows on certain material surfaces getting stuck when quick-toggling shadows.
Fixed: Several XUI warnings in a bunch of floaters.
Fixed: Warning about top toolbar tooltip missing.
Fixed: Bad middle segment toolbar button scaling.
Fixed: SSR Resolution slider duplicate in preferences - display.
Fixed: Release Notes popup link after update.
Removed: HTTP Inventory option from Preferences.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.6
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="206"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Manually added RLVa back into the Viewer. Might need fixing.
Added: All necessary RLVa debugs.
Changed: Replaced llmin(llmax()) with the much simpler llclamp.
Changed: LLZoomer to set the zoom to 0.9 of the current value instead of dividing 1 by 1.1.
Changed: Massive Overhaul to the flycam code.
Changed: Clamped camera movement more reliable with extreme variable framerates.
Changed: Xbox360 Controller defaults a bit to match the new altered movement speed.
Changed: Enabled RLVa tab in Preferences.
Changed: Enabled RLVa submenu in Dragon main menu.
Changed: Version to 2.6.
Fixed: Stand/Stop/Flying button not clickable.
Fixes: Camera preset sliders not refreshing when pressing default.
Fixed: Zoom not taking effect immediately when smoothing is still active from previous smoothed zoom movement.
Fixed: Lineendings.
Fixed: RLVa, Compile.
Merge with RLVa.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.5.6
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="257"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Option to toggle Motion Blur between "Everything" , "My Avatar &amp; Objects" , "Objects Only".
Added: Option to control Screen Space Reflection's brightness.
Added: Selective De-Fullbright menu option, per feedback.
Changed: Unlocked already prepared SSR Brightness option in Machinima Sidebar.
Changed: Massive overhaul of the "Edit Shape" panel. Breaking all other edit wearables, they need fixing too.
Changed: Removed 3D previews of shape edit.
Changed: Made shape edit sliders much smaller and use less extra gap pixels between them.
Changed: Snapshot floater "Refresh" button label to "NEW SNAP" for when we translate it.
Changed: More Edit Wearables layout changes and layout consistency fixes.
Changed: Made some consistency changes to COF wearables panel to fit in with the other recent changes.
Changed: Version to 2.5.6
Fixed: Impostors being included in Motion Blur rendering.
Fixed (Workaround): Region Water flickering when its near the far clip plane with enabled Object Object Occlusion.
Fixed: Stand button clipping outside the Movement floater.
Fixed: Warns in floater_moveview.xml.
Fixed: Warns in panel_outfit_gallery.xml.
Fixed: Conversations button flashing forever.
Fixed: Alt keybinds having their mask and key strings on the wrong size creating weird labels.
Fixed: Newly introduced temp attachments tab broke the layout in Appearance - Outfits.
Merge with Bento RC
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.5.5
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="389"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Changed: Stop cloud and water ripple movement while freezing the world.
Changed: Made sure Deferred shaders can only be toggled with Deferred enabled.
Changed: Made sure shadow maps can only be quick-allocated with Deferred enabled.
Changed: Make fast-toggling shaders return a proper value in case we ever want to use it for something.
Changed: Disallow setting any memory higher than 1992 or lower than 128 to prevent memory issues.
Changed: Limit the memory slider min value to 128mb and the max to 1992 in case the code doesn't do it.
Changed: Open the Appearance floater with the "My Outfits" tab instead of the "Outfit Gallery".
Changed: Moved chat tags into the avatar name cache call, should fix a rare case if tags being reverted/missing.
Changed: Use the GLManager's VRAM as max and include SL's usage into the memory calculations when not using a NVidia Card.
Changed: Disable Object Object Occlusion by default. (We might want to enable this in case of AMD Card)
Changed: Disable Spellcheck by default.
Changed: Version to 2.5.5
Fixed: Self-inflicted issue that broke toasting when local chat is in Convo floater and Convo floater is closed.
Fixed: (QUICKFIX) Sidebar vanishing when toggled off instead of sliding out.
Fixed: Toggling Godrays with Deferred disabled causes the Viewer to crash.
Fixed: Toggling SSR with Deferred disabled causes the Viewer to crash.
Fixed: Toggling Blur Light with Deferred disabled causes the Viewer to crash.
Fixed: Toggling SSAO with Deferred disabled causes the Viewer to crash.
Fixed: Toggling Shadows with Deferred disabled causes the Viewer to crash.
Fixed: Changing shadow resolution caused the shadow detail option to revert to its previous value.
Fixed: Only refresh and draw the Machinima Sidebar when its really visible but respect the slide animation.
Misc: Machinima Sidebar code cleanup.
Misc: Code Cleanup. Line Endings.
Misc: Make resetDeferredShaders() return a value so we can use it as boolean.
Misc: Made toggling shadows return a proper value in case we ever want to use it for something.
Misc: Massive preferences XML file cleanups.
Misc: Cleanup in sidebar XML files.
Misc: Slight code cleanup in llimview and llviewercontrol.
Misc: Cleanup some debugging code in llfloaterpreferences.
Merge with Bento
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.5.4
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="90"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Shadow Resolution sliders to Machinima Sidebar.
Added: Screen Space Reflection Brightness slider to Machinima Sidebar. (Coming Soon)
Changed: Make progress panel background only appear when logging in.
Changed: Made Machinima Sidebar able to utilize coded functions.
Changed: Made Machinima Sidebar use the vector4 and vector3 functions to allow changing them properly.
Changed: Version to 2.5.4.
Misc: Line Endings and Code Cleanup.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.5.3
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="220"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: VRAM usage display to preferences.
Added: Changelog text block for 2.5.3. Template changes, need to fill in later.
Changed: Camera smoothness to it's intended default value.
Changed: Custom System Memory to be the default, force 128mb by default in code.
Changed: Texture console VRAM display, show colored segments to indicate what's taken by SL and what isn't.
Changed: Texture console memory display, renamed bars to Scene and System to match preferences.
Changed: Replaced the progress bar textures with more fitting ones.
Changed: Made Progress Screen transparent, changed it's layout for the new progressbar texture.
Changed: Moved OpenGL 3.0 Texture Compression option to top.
Changed: Made System and Scene Memory slider change max value depending on the available memory.
Changed: Default value of Scene Memory Debug to 256mb.
Changed: Made labeling for System Memory and GPU Memory Usage more clear.
Changed: Version to 2.5.3.
Fixed: Compile
Removed: Custom System Memory option.
Removed: Custom System Memory option from preferences.
Merge with Bento
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.5.2
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="25"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Changed: Version to 2.5.2.
Merge with Linden VLC Release
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.5.1
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="480"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Pie Menu popup animation speed option to ui preferences.
Added: Chat history name background tagging for Mod + Dev and Developer only.
Changed: Pie Menu popup animation look.
Changed: Made alpha/dealpha able to alpha/dealpha single faces and multiple selected faces from different objects.
Changed: SSAO defaults, slightly less strong when multiple corners are close together.
Changed: Version to 2.5.1.
Changed: Login panel layout, added toggleable changelog.
Misc: Code tagging.
              </text>
       </panel>
       </scroll_container>
      </layout_panel>
  </layout_stack>
  
  <panel
  follows="right|left|bottom"
  height="150"
  layout="topleft"
  left="0"
  name="panel_login2"
  focus_root="true" 
  bottom="-1"
  width="996">
    <layout_stack
    border_size="0"
    follows="all"
    height="150"
    layout="topleft"
    left="0"
    mouse_opaque="true"
    name="root_stack"
    orientation="horizontal"
    top="0"
    width="996">
      <layout_panel
      auto_resize="true"
      follows="all"
      height="120"
      layout="topleft"
      mouse_opaque="true"
      name="info_panel"
      top_pad="0"
      width="200">
       <button
       follows="left|top"
       height="18"
       control_name="ShowChangelogs"
       is_toggle="true"
       image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
        image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
       label="Changelogs"
       font="SansSerif"
       font.style="BOLD"
       layout="topleft"
       left="1"
       halign="center"
       name="version_info_link"
       top="17"
       width="120"/>
       <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left|right"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left_pad="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top="25"
    width="78"/>
      </layout_panel>
      <layout_panel
      auto_resize="false"
      follows="all"
      height="130"
      layout="topleft"
      mouse_opaque="true"
      name="root_panel"
      top_pad="0"
      width="395">
       
       <text
        follows="left|top|right"
        font="SansSerifBig"
        font_shadow="soft"
        font.style="BOLD"
        halign="center"
        height="20"
        top="0"
        left="0"
        name="app_name_text"
        width="380"
        word_wrap="true">
[APP_NAME]
        </text>
       
       <button
        follows="left|top"
        height="18"
        control_name="PreferencesLogin"
        image_overlay_alignment="left"
        pad_bottom="0"
        image_overlay="Command_Preferences_Icon"
        image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
        image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
        label="Preferences"
        is_toggle="false"
        font="SansSerif"
        font.style="BOLD"
        label_color="1 1 1 0.7"
        layout="topleft"
        left="1"
        halign="center"
        name="pref_btn"
        top="17"
        width="122">
              <button.commit_callback
              function="Floater.Toggle"
              parameter="preferences"/>
        </button>
        <!--<button
        follows="right|top"
        height="18"
        image_overlay_alignment="left"
        image_bottom_pad="1"
        pad_bottom="0"
        image_overlay="Command_Profile_Icon"
        image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
        image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
        label="Sign Up"
        font="SansSerif"
        font.style="BOLD"
        label_color="1 1 1 0.7"
        layout="topleft"
        left_pad="1"
        halign="center"
        name="create_new_account_text"
        top_delta="0"
        width="100"/>-->
        <!--<button
        follows="right|top"
        height="18"
        image_unselected="transparentj2c"
        image_selected="transparentj2c"
        label="Forgot Login details?"
        font="SansSerifBig"
        font.style="BOLD"
        label_color="1 1 1 0.7"
        layout="topleft"
        left="0"
        halign="right"
        name="forgot_password_text"
        top_pad="0"
        width="100"/>-->
        <button
        follows="right|top"
        height="18"
        image_overlay_alignment="left"
        pad_bottom="0"
        image_overlay="Command_AboutLand_Icon"
        image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
        image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
        label="Grid Status"
        font="SansSerif"
        font.style="BOLD"
        label_color="1 1 1 0.7"
        layout="topleft"
        left_pad="1"
        halign="center"
        name="grid_btn"
        top_delta="0"
        width="111">
        <button.commit_callback
          function="PromptShowURL"
          parameter="WebLaunchExternalTarget,http://status.secondlifegrid.net/"/>
        </button>
        <combo_box
        allow_text_entry="true"
        follows="left|top"
        height="18"
        max_chars="256"
        layout="topleft"
        label="Select a Grid"
        top_delta="0"
        left_pad="1"
        name="server_combo"
        width="157"
        visible="true">
          <combo_box.combo_editor
          font="SansSerif"
          font.style="BOLD"
          font_shadow="soft"
          text_tentative_color="0.7 0.7 0.7 0.7"
          cursor_color="White"
          text_color="0.75 0.75 0.75 0.7"
          background_image="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
          background_image_disabled="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
          background_image_focused="Toolbar_Middle_Off"/>
          <combo_box.combo_button
          scale_image="true"
          image_overlay="R"
          image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Dropdown_Off"
          image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Dropdown_Selected"
          image_disabled="Toolbar_Middle_Dropdown_Off" />
            <combo_box.combo_list
              bg_writeable_color="White_02"
              background_visible="true"/>
        </combo_box>
        <line_editor
        commit_on_focus_lost="false"
        follows="left|top"
        height="22"
        label="Username"
        left="113"
        tool_tip="The username you chose when you registered, like bobsmith12 or Steller Sunshine"
        top_pad="12"
        name="username_combo"
        width="152"/>
        <line_editor
        follows="left|top"
        commit_on_focus_lost="false"
        height="22"
        max_length_bytes="16"
        name="password_edit"
        label="Password"
        is_password="true" 
        select_on_focus="true"
        left_delta="0"
        top_pad="3"
        width="152" />
        <check_box
        control_name="RememberPassword"
        follows="left|top"
        font="SansSerifSmall"
        height="18"
        left_pad="0"
        label="remember"
        top_delta="2"
        name="remember_check"
        width="200"/>
        <combo_box
        allow_text_entry="true"
        control_name="LoginLocation"
        follows="left|top"
        height="23"
        max_chars="128"
        top_pad="5"
        left="113"
        name="start_location_combo"
        width="152">
          <combo_box.combo_editor
          background_image="TextField_Off"
          background_image_disabled="TextField_Disabled"
          background_image_focused="TextField_Active"/>
          <combo_box.item
          label="My last location"
          name="MyLastLocation"
          value="last" />
          <combo_box.item
          label="My home"
          name="MyHome"
          value="home" />
          <combo_box.item
          label="&lt;Type region name&gt;"
          name="Typeregionname"
          value="" />
          <combo_box.combo_button
          scale_image="true"
          image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
          image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
          image_pressed="Toolbar_Middle_Selected" 
          image_pressed_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
          image_overlay="DownArrow_Off"/>
          <combo_box.drop_down_button
          scale_image="false"
          image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Unselected"
          image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
          image_pressed="Toolbar_Middle_Selected" 
          image_pressed_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
          image_disabled="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"/>
        </combo_box>
       <button
       follows="left|top"
       height="23"
       image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
       image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
       label="RAWR!"
       font="SansSerif"
       font.style="BOLD"
       label_color="1 1 1 0.8"
       layout="topleft"
       left="113"
       name="connect_btn"
       top_pad="3"
       width="152"/>
      </layout_panel>
      <layout_panel
      auto_resize="true"
      follows="all"
      height="100"
      layout="topleft"
      mouse_opaque="true"
      name="help_panel"
      top_pad="0"
      width="200">
       <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left|right"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="0"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top="25"
    width="120"/>
       <button
        follows="right|top"
        height="18"
        control_name="FirstStart"
        image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
        image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
        label="Quit"
        font="SansSerif"
        font.style="BOLD"
        label_color="1 1 1 0.7"
        layout="topleft"
        left_pad="1"
        halign="center"
        name="quit_btn"
        top_delta="-8"
        width="77"/>
      </layout_panel>
    </layout_stack>
  </panel>
</panel>
