<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<panel
follows="all"
height="600"
layout="topleft"
left="0"
name="panel_login"
focus_root="false" 
top="600"
 width="996">
<panel.string name="create_account_url">
       http://join.secondlife.com/
</panel.string>
<string name="reg_in_client_url" translate="false">
     http://secondlife.eniac15.lindenlab.com/reg-in-client/
</string>
<panel.string name="forgot_password_url">
       http://secondlife.com/account/request.php
</panel.string>
  <web_browser
  visibility_control="ExperimentalLogin"
  tab_stop="false" 
  trusted_content="true" 
  bg_opaque_color="Black"
  border_visible="false"
  top="-600"
  follows="all"
  start_url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/53euICErnVg?autoplay=1&amp;loop=1&amp;playlist=53euICErnVg"
  left="0"
  name="html"
  height="650"
  width="996" />
  
  <!--<icon
  follows="all"
  height="600"
  image_name="Login_BG"
  color="1 1 1 1"
  layout="topleft"
  name="login_bg"
  mouse_opaque="false"
  visible="true"
  width="1016"
  left="0"
  top="-600"/>-->
  <icon
  follows="bottom|left|right"
  height="125"
  image_name="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
  color="0.15 0.05 0 1"
  layout="topleft"
  name="login_bg"
  mouse_opaque="false"
  visible="true"
  width="996"
  left="0"
  top="-125"/>
  <icon
  follows="bottom|left|right"
  height="125"
  image_name="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
  color="0 0 0 1"
  layout="topleft"
  name="login_bg"
  mouse_opaque="false"
  visible="true"
  width="996"
  left="0"
  top="-125"/>
  
  <icon
  follows="top|left|right"
  height="20"
  image_name="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
  color="0 0 0 1"
  layout="topleft"
  name="login_bg"
  mouse_opaque="false"
  visible="true"
  width="996"
  left="0"
  top="0"/>
  <icon
  follows="top|left|right"
  height="20"
  image_name="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
  color="0.15 0.05 0 1"
  layout="topleft"
  name="login_bg"
  mouse_opaque="false"
  visible="true"
  width="996"
  left="0"
  top="0"/>
  <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left|right"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top="20"
    width="994"/>
  <button
       follows="left|top|right"
       height="20"
       image_unselected="transparentj2c"
       image_selected="transparentj2c"
       label="[CHANNEL] [VERSION] - [2.9.2 - Bit Dragon]"
       font="SansSerifSmall"
       layout="topleft"
       left="3"
       halign="left"
       name="channel_text"
       top="1"
       width="994">
       <button.commit_callback
         function="Floater.Show"
         parameter="sl_about"/>
       </button>
  <layout_stack
    border_size="0"
    follows="all"
    height="445"
    layout="topleft"
    left="0"
    mouse_opaque="false"
    name="root_stack"
    orientation="vertical"
    top="20"
    width="998">
      <layout_panel
      auto_resize="true"
      visibility_control="ShowChangelogs"
      follows="all"
      height="490"
      layout="topleft"
      mouse_opaque="false"
      name="info_panel"
      top_pad="0"
      width="998">
       <scroll_container
       color="Transparent"
       follows="all"
       layout="topleft"
       mouse_opaque="false"
       left="0"
       name="camera_scroll"
       opaque="true"
       height="487"
       width="994"
       top="3">
       <panel
       follows="top|left"
       height="9175"
       layout="topleft"
       left="0"
       name="panel_login2"
       top="0"
       width="980">
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="324"
              top="10"
              left="7"
              max_length="9999"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: DracO HirudO and Ken Durham to patron list.
Added: Triangle (polygon) count to "Avatar Rendering Complexity" display.
Added: Triangle (polygon) count to Object Weights window.
Added: Worn tab to Inventory window.
Added: Filter type dropdown to Inventory window.
Added: Akritos Rain to the Patreon list.
Added: Ability to set objects or faces to fullbright locally.
Added: Ability to change object or face alpha modes locally.
Added: Dhalgren Correia to the Patreon list.
Added: Max FPS option to Preferences - Display tab.
Changed: Overhauled Object Weights window layout.
Changed: Overhauled Inventory Filter window layout.
Changed: Hide the "Edit" menu while the recent tab is active.
Changed: Moved alpha and fullbright manipulation options into a detachable sub menu.
Changed: Merged de/realpha and alpha mode codes into one big function to be used and simplified it.
Changed: Version to 2.9.2.
Fixed: Compile.
Fixed: Several entries from the People menus that were not functional.
Fixed: Several entries from the People menus that did not check properly when an option was enabled.
Fixed: Vignette options being cut off.
Fixed: L$ Balance blocking the inventory menu.
Removed: Several entries from the People menus that did not exist.
Removed: Unneeded code in llviewerobjectlist.cpp.
Misc: Cleaned up llpanelmaininventory.cpp a bit.
Misc: Cleaned up llpanelpeople.cpp/h a bit.
Merge with Viewer Bear
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.9.1
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="338"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              max_length="9999"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: EaseIn and EaseOut times info display to Animation Manipulator window.
Added: Patreon support section to "About Black Dragon" window for all supporters.
Added: Ability to preview .anim files from disk inworld on your avatar by creating local animations to play with the Animation Manipulator.
Added: Maddy to the list of patrons.
Added: First babysteps and preparations for pose exporter.
Added: More Patreon patrons to the About Black Dragon window.
Changed: Added a bunch of missing login panel changes to the changelog.
Changed: Overhauled Inventory window layout.
Changed: Marketplace Inbox button into a bottom button.
Changed: Improved SSR look and quality.
Changed: Overhauled People window layout.
Changed: Simplified more formatting code in the Animation Manipulator window.
Changed: Disabled the Admin main menu.
Changed: Moved marketplace and grid status menu entries to the browser menu.
Changed: Made the favoritebar able to contain technically any object (landmarks and callingcards for now).
Changed: Layout of About Black Dragon window a bit, broadened tabs and moved Patreon tab to second position.
Changed: Version to 2.9.1.
Fixed: XML warnings in log when opening an animation.
Fixed: Inconsistencies in group list items.
Fixed: Member ban button in group panel clipping into other buttons.
Removed: Sort buttons in Inventory.
Removed: All buttons except the remove button.
Misc: Cleaned up People window code.
Misc: Cleaned up the bdposingmotion.cpp a bit.
Misc: Cleaned up bdfloateranimations.cpp some more.
Misc: Increment version to 5.1.1 for auto-updater purposes.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.9.0
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="1287"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              max_length="9999"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Tooltips for every single option in display tab.
Added: Report (someone) option to people and conversation menus.
Added: Missing default button for SSR Resolution.
Added: Tooltips and improved existing tooltips in the 'Interface' preferences tab.
Added: Change keybinding button to 'Keybindings' preferences tab.
Added: Tooltips and improved existing tooltips in the 'IM &amp; Groupchat' preferences tab.
Added: Tooltips and improved existing tooltips in the 'Camera' preferences tab.
Added: (mass) Reset Skeleton, (mass) Reset Skeleton and Animations, Derender, Mute Voice and Block Text options to 'People' window right-click menu.
Added: View Chat History, Remove Friend, Share, Mute Voice and Block Text options to inworld avatar right-click menu.
Added: View Chat History, Remove Friend, Share, Mute Voice and Block Text options to inworld avatar attachment right-click menu.
Added: Request Teleport, View Chat History and Report options to group member list right-click menu.
Added: Ability to bind 'Move Left' and 'Move Right' to sitting binds for vehicle controls.
Added: Shift + A, Shift + D, Shift + Left Arrow and Shift + Right Arrow to sitting controls to fix gear shifting on some vehicles.
Added: Tooltips and improved existing tooltips in the 'Notifications' preferences tab.
Added: Tooltips and improved existing tooltips in the 'Controls' preferences tab.
Added: Tooltips and improved existing tooltips in the 'General' preferences tab.
Added: Tooltips and improved existing tooltips in the 'Privacy' preferences tab.
Added: Tooltips and improved existing tooltips in the 'Sound &amp; Media' preferences tab.
Added: Tooltips and improved existing tooltips in the 'Keybindings' preferences tab.
Added: Separator between the 'close conversation' menu entry and all others in the conversation tab menu.
Added: Tooltips and improved existing tooltips in the 'Viewer' preferences tab.
Added: Tooltips and improved existing tooltips in the 'Chat' preferences tab.
Added: Tooltips and improved existing tooltips in the 'Browser' preferences tab.
Added: Tooltips and improved existing tooltips in the 'RLVa' preferences tab.
Added: Buttons for adding wait and repeat events directly to the Animator.
Added: Tooltips to most buttons of the Animator.
Added: Ability to change wait event times.
Added: Missing group ban button in group 'Roles' panel.
Added: Additional info display for EaseIn/Out duration of animations in the 'Motions' tab.
Changed: More Icon changes and fixes.
Changed: Improved shadow precision on distance, on high altitudes and eliminate almost all cases of shadows flickering on high altitudes.
Changed: Version to 2.9.0 - Bit Dragon.
Changed: Allow hyperlinks in tooltips.
Changed: Disabled max Texture\Scene Memory clamping.
Changed: Posing animation to an empty all-bone using animation.
Changed: Tooltip layout and look.
Changed: Disabled german display tab for now.
Changed: Don't refresh our window when changing the UI size, it doesn't fix the offset.
Changed: Agent recorder file path to user_settings rather than the often read-only Viewer folder. Should fix agent recorder sometimes not working.
Changed: Improved tooltips in display tab with additional information and a consistent design.
Changed: Don't alter our camera behavior when ClickToWalk is enabled.
Changed: Allow zooming out 9999m.
Changed: Updated login screen changelog.
Changed: Default button appearance to make it clearer which options they affect (if they affect multiple for instance).
Changed: Improved all tooltips for the onscreen movement control window.
Changed: Disabled german translation for the 'Interface' preferences tab.
Changed: Disabled foot shadow texture.
Changed: Layout and style of the 'Sound &amp; Media' preferences tab to fit all other tabs.
Changed: Show text and allow text entry for volume sliders.
Changed: Disabled german translation for the 'Sound &amp; Media' preferences tab.
Changed: Disabled german translation for the 'IM &amp; Groupchat' preferences tab.
Changed: Disabled german translation for the 'Camera' preferences tab.
Changed: Improved Volumetric Lighting slightly, removed random noise completely.
Changed: Completely overhauled and reorganized all most used avatar related right-click menus into a consistent layout.
Changed: Simplified the bone value display formatting code.
Changed: Moved 'Derender' option in avatar right click menus to main menu rather than the 'Render Avatar' submenu.
Changed: Renamed 'Ignore' in SLURL-based right click menus to 'Block All' for consistency.
Changed: Overhauled 'Animation' tab in Animation Controls window for better space usage and workflow.
Changed: Added latest changes to the loginscreen changelog.
Changed: Disabled the Launcher notification each Viewer start for now.
Changed: A few chat option labels since we now have proper tooltips for them.
Changed: Further improvements on the 'Display' tab tooltips, specifically highlighting values and giving extended info whether they are the SL ultra setting or not.
Changed: Layout of animator tab in 'Animation Controls' window for a better workflow.
Changed: The way the Animator behaves when adding new events, now selects the added entry rather than the previous.
Changed: Disabled all german preferences panel translations for now.
Changed: Moved the 'Animation Control' menu entry into 'My Useful Features' and renamed it to 'Pose/Animation Manipulator'.
Changed: Consistency pass over some preferences tooltips.
Changed: Moved estate management menu entries in right click menus to the avatar actions.
Changed: Disabled memory limitations on AMD cards.
Changed: Updated the login panel changelog with the latest bugfixes.
Fixed: Compile and all Fmodex linking errors.
Fixed: Viewer using Second Life icons instead of Black Dragon's.
Fixed: Projector lights vanishing on distance.
Fixed: Current Outfit tab not displaying attachments.
Fixed: Line Endings in llwindow.h.
Fixed: Line Endings in llwindowheadless.h.
Fixed: Line Endings in llwindowwin32.h.
Fixed: Crash when trying to manipulate an Avatar via the Animation Controls window that is no longer available.
Fixed: SSR Brightness default button reverting SSR Resolution instead.
Fixed: Default button for projector shadow resolution being off.
Fixed: Missing header of the german interface tab.
Fixed: Info (i) buttons in namelists clipping outside the name entry.
Fixed: Double\Triple\Quad default button height offset in 'Camera' preferences tab.
Fixed: Double\Triple\Quad default button height offset in 'Graphics' preferences tab.
Fixed: Posing motion being overriden by priority 4 animations, make the posing animation have priority 7.
Fixed: Some 'Change Selected' buttons not working properly in 'Keybindings' tab.
Fixed: 'Keybindings' panel layout and alignment.
Fixed: Notification embed option in RLVa tab not working.
Fixed: A bunch of dummy warnings all over the place.
Fixed: Longstanding issue with HUDs not being clickable through the top toolbar.
Removed: Check for Updates button in About Black Dragon floater.
Removed: Double default button in 'Notifications' preferences tab.
Removed: Deprecated Enable 'FirstRLVGiveToRLV' Warning option.
Misc: Merge and fixes.
Misc: More compile fixes.
Misc: Branding and naming changes for 64bit.
Misc: Cleanup in bdfloateranimations.cpp.
Misc: Massive cleanup in preferences floater code.
Merge with Alex Ivy
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.8.2
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="169"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="490"
              word_wrap="false">
Changed: Disabled Regiolight and Daycycle by default.
Changed: Allow the alpha depth inclusion option to work when Volumetric Lighting is enabled but DoF isn't.
Changed: Raised default Texture Memory and System Memory to 512m, should lessen texture trashing when starting for the first time.
Changed: Slightly tuned glow settings, slightly weaker glow to fix Greedy Greedy's horrible usage of fullbright and glow and prevent it from being unreadable.
Changed: Per Adeon's request: Reduced collapsed topbar to a minimum size and make it OCD friendly.
Changed: Tweaked toast popup space from top toolbar slightly.
Changed: Updated Warning triggers thresholds in preferences to factor in the new defaults.
Changed: Version to 2.8.2.
Fixed: Render Own Attached Lights option in Machinima Sidebar not working.
Fixed: Pie menu not closing when clicking into the center hole.
Fixed: Don't render invisible surfaces with glow, shadows will no longer be cast either.
Removed: Unused Bottom Pad option in chat tab.
Removed: Bottom Space option double in alerts tab.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.8.1
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="221"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="490"
              word_wrap="false">
Changed: Reduced default draw distance from 256m to 96m.
Changed: Disabled automasking in non deferred by default.
Changed: Disabled automasking in deferred by default.
Changed: Increased default Tree Quality to 'Normal'.
Changed: Increased default Object Quality to 'Normal'.
Changed: Increased default Reflection Quality to 'Normal'.
Changed: Reduced default projector shadow resolutions to 1024x1024.
Changed: Disable showing the edit particle beam and hand motion by default.
Changed: Default cloud noise texture to 'Cumolo Nimbus'.
Changed: Moved toast top corner region a bit up after floater container changes.
Changed: Increased precision of several glow and tone mapping sliders and reweighted some min/max values.
Changed: Version to 2.8.1.
Fixed: Corrected missing tone mapping tweak.
Fixed: Line Endings in several files.
Fixed: Floaters not snapping to the edges of the screen but to wrong ghost edges.
Fixed: Vignette slider option text input field being cut off slightly.
Fixed: Added missing changelog entries.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.8.0
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="311"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="490"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Timestamp for Avatar Render entries in Avatar Mute Settings tab.
Added: Auto Complete Gestures option to Chat tab.
Changed: Default Avatar Surface Derender limit to 200m²
Changed: Default Object Surface Derender limit to 256m².
Changed: Improved auto fly on login tooltip a bit.
Changed: Add button in animation tab to add after the selected entry.
Changed: Chat tab layout, reordered a few options to match better with other options.
Changed: Moved down main view floater rectangle a bit, prevents floaters from covering the topbar.
Changed: Improved Animator list entry addition code.
Changed: Version to 2.8.0 - Bone Dragon.
Changed: Improved Tone Mapping defaults for a brighter, whiter image.
Changed: Glow defaults for a warmer and softer image.
Fixed: Disabling Fullbrights globally will result in the fullbright flag being updated on editable objects when editing them.
Fixed: Statusbar FPS counter displaying more FPS than we actually get.
Fixed: Shift + Home (highlight from current position to start) shortcut not working when "Arrow Keys Move" is enabled.
Fixed: Eject, Freeze, Dump XML and Debug pie menu slices not enabling when they should.
Fixed: Corrected leftover tooltip from Nirans Viewer for auto login.
Fixed (POTENTIAL): Random access violation crash in pie menu when right clicking yourself while sitting.
Fixed: Compile.
Fixed: Repeats not able to go into negatives.
Fixed: Owner label in Tools floater not using SLURL anymore.
Misc: Tweaks to popup code in pie menu.
Misc: Patchnote fixes.
Merge with Release. (100+ changes)
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.7.9
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="220"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: 1080p, 4K and 6K preset resolutions to local snapshot resolution dropdown.
Added: First working implementation of the Animator, capable of waiting, repeating and playing all saved poses.
Added: Options to render your own attached lights and inworld lights.
Added: Option to toggle light coming from projectors.
Changed: Switched answer button labels for System UI Scale notification.
Changed: Behavior of light options to be independent from each other. All 3 need to be enabled to see all lights.
Changed: Inworld Poser to 5.0.
- Added: Ability to toggle bone overrides on and off.
- Added: Ability to save bone overrides into pose presets.
- Changed: Layout of Animation Control floater to its (semi) final design.
- Changed: Font style to bold when a bone is enabled. Normal if its disabled.
- Fixed: Crash when using Reset Skeleton and Animations while posing.
- Fixed: Last HindLimb becoming corrupt sometimes.
- Removed: Some debugging log texts.
Changed: Version to 2.7.9.
Fixed: "Com(p)lexity" label in Dragon menu. Again.
Fixed: Warning in floater_preview_notecard.xml.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.7.8
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="390"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Show number of agents not being able to see you.
Added: First steps of the planned Animator. (WIP)
Added: Multi-selection delete for poses.
Added: Internal blend timer for motions to be used for linear interpolation.
Changed: Massive rewrite and cleanup of the Animation Controls floater.
- Made linear interpolation default.
- Linear interpolation to be constant interpolation.
- Cleaned up and consolidated multiple quick functions into one big command function.
- Made use of the ability to add objects and pointers to list entries to simplify a lot of character find loops.
- Fixed UnFreeze unable to unfreeze only the selected avatars.
Changed: Decapitalized capitalistic letters in object weight info floater. Damn capitalists.
Changed: Layout of build options floater (grid options).
Changed: Clamp spherical linear interpolation between 0.0 and 1.0. Isn't conveyed in the UI yet.
Changed: Disabled all animator controls for now.
Changed: Sharpened godray shadow corners, less dittering but might look worse on lower shadow resolutions.
Changed: Version to 2.7.8.
Fixed: FXAA Warning appearing on wrong conditions.
Fixed: Titles in additional object info being almost unreadable.
Fixed: Developer auto-response message appearing for others when opening my group.
Fixed: Some options in Machinima Sidebar being enabled with Deferred instead of their correct feature.
Fixed: (POTENTIAL) AMD not reporting its max and used memory correctly in the texture console.
Fixed: Glow Warmth Weight sliders in preferences not refreshing their correct values.
Fixed: Linear interpolation behaving weird and being unreliable.
Fixed: (POTENTIAL) Attempted fix at writing bogus bone.
Fixed: Changing interpolation type and time resulting in a bogus XML file or header.
Fixed: Inverted vehicle controls.
Removed: Greyscale effect on teleport, for now.
Misc: Changed, added and removed some commenting.
Misc: Optimizations in People floater to reduce getChild calls.
Misc: Improved Motion Blur impostor check and removed some unnecessary extra Settings getter.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.7.7
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="443"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Always Render Friends option to Preferences - Display tab.
Changed: Finetuned Tone Mapping brightness a bit more, slightly darker, still brighter than before.
Changed: Dropped Motion Blur types down to only objects and your own avatar by default.
Changed: Improved description of all warnings in Preferences - Display tab.
Changed: Allowed Auto Hide Surface Limit to go up to 512m².
Changed: Made hitting ESC (reset view) disable Third Person Steering.
Changed: Hide Sidebar while in Mouselook.
Changed: Made animation window refresh bones after clicking Start Posing.
Changed: Clamp view angle slider in Machinima Sidebar to min and max current camera values.
Changed: Some conditions for warnings appearing.
Changed: Made all boolean warnings appear via UI calls, saves a lot calls.
Changed: Made FPS counter refresh only 10 times a second instead of as fast as possible. (Subject to change).
Changed: Made "Start Posing" reflect it's current status and show "Stop Posing" when enabled.
Changed: Enable Highlight Friend Names by default.
Changed: Disable bone rotation controls as long as posing is not enabled.
Changed: Version to 2.7.7.
Fixed: Sky Quality and Reflection Quality warnings being in the wrong section.
Fixed: Short massive framedrop/freeze when going into Mouselook with hide UI in ML enabled.
Fixed: Stopping all animations with the animation window breaks posing.
Fixed: Y Bone Rotation sliders writing Z rotations into the list resulting in them being saved/loaded wrong in poses.
Fixed: Bone refresh showing the current in-transition values instead of the final values.
Fixed: Conversation log combobox not being detected and throwing an warning.
Misc: Cleaned up llfloaterpreferences.cpp slightly.
Misc: Cleaned up bdfloateranimations.cpp a bit.
Misc: Fixed up a whitespace in llfloaterimsession.cpp.
Misc: Massive performance optimizations to sidebar refreshing.
Misc: Massive Performance optimizations to preferences window.
- Eliminated a massive amount of getChild calls every update.
- Eliminated a massive amount of gSavedSettings setting getter calls every refresh.
- Reduced graphic options and memory refreshs to once every second.
- Performance with preferences open (even with display tab selected) shows almost similar performance as with preferences closed now.
Misc: Slight performance improvements for People floater refreshes.
Misc: Slight performance improvements on updating the display stats such as avg FPS and used memory being logged.
Misc: Cleanup and comment llagentcamera.cpp, llstatusbar.h and lltoolpie.cpp a bit.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.7.6
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="208"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Changed: Inworld Poser to Version 4.0.
- Inworld Poser can now change pelvis position.
- Inworld Poser can now interpolate positions.
- Inworld Poser can now be customized to use linear or spherical linear interpolation.
- Inworld Poser can now save interpolation strength and type into the exported XML.
- Added: Double click to load a pose.
- Added: Controls to add interpolation type and strength when saving a pose.
- Added: Position sliders and display in the bone list.
- Changed: Pose tab layout and buttons.
- Changed: Moved save button and name editor to pose tab.
- Changed: Cut off more than 3 decimal digits on rotation and position values.
- Fixed: Poser not creating a folder automatically if needed.
- Misc: Cleaned up and commented some poser code.
Changed: Slightly brightened pitch black colors up with Tone Mapping, to allow black clothes to show their texture details.
Changed: Version to 2.7.6.
Fixed: Depth of Field lock shortcut not properly triggering, changed it to Shift + Alt + X.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.7.5
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="142"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Changed: Disabled torso rotation on head tracking.
Changed: Inworld Poser to Version 3.0
- Inworld Poser can now save/load and delete poses. (XML)
- Inworld Poser will now blend from one pose to another.
- Inworld Poser will now blend between rotation changes.
- Changed rotations to euler angles instead of converted vector3
- Fixed body inflating with certain rotation thresholds.
- Fixed rotations strength scaling weird near -1/1.
- Changed slider min/max values to 3.142 (PI).
- Cleaned up and reorganized a bit of code.
Changed: Version to 2.7.5.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.7.4
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="64"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Changed: Inworld Poser to Version 2.0.
- Poser can now rotate all 133 bones in the LL skeleton.
Changed: Poser tab layout.
Changed: Version to 2.7.4.
Removed: Poser debugs.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.7.3
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="246"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Inworld Poser feature to Animation Control floater.
- Stops all default standing animations.
- Plays a custom animation that tells the Viewer to apply your specified bone rotations.
- Allows rotating every available, important non-bento (coming in next version) bone freely via the UI.
- Comes with default buttons to quickly reset a bone back to the default position.
- Debugs are permanent, so is the pose, the Pose will save over sessions and needs to be manually resetted for now.
- This feature is completely local.
- Future updates include, exporting, multi-pose and blending between them (animations) and possibly more.
Added: A whole lot of debugs for the Poser.
Added: Ability for Animation Control floater to access Vector3 controls properly.
Added: Logging to find out about future 3D mice we might want to add.
Changed: Removed iteration through avatars when the only one the feature is going to affect is ourselves.
Changed: Decreased the visible surface amount needed for the Machinima Sidebar to start rendering. e.g doesn't vanish in the last bit.
Changed: Version to 2.7.3.
Fixed: Mislabeled code comment.
Fixed: A whole lot of warnings in "Picks" floater.
Fixed: Joystick always resetting to Xbox360 Controls.
Fixed: A whole bunch of warnings in "Places" floater.
Fixed: Compile. Missing bdposingmotion.h/cpp in CMakeLists.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.7.2
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="326"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Changed: Improved texture console display. Match memory type colors and grey out unavailable memory.
Changed: Only allow animation manipulation of people whose "Can Edit My Objects" permission we got.
- This includes saving and applying animations to/from them.
- Stopping, restarting and altering speed is not subject to these changes.
Changed: Re-enabled animation manipulation window.
Changed: Moved Avatar Render Settings to main preferences as tab.
Changed: Disallow animating others via the animation control window.
Changed: Greyed out text color for already accepted attachments from notifications.
Changed: Better text color for notification main text.
Changed: Overhauled "Keybindings" preferences tab layout.
Changed: Moved all action lists below its corresponding mode.
Changed: "Add" and "Remove" buttons to be seperate for each mode.
Changed: Disallow opening the bind window when no action is selected.
Changed: Version to 2.7.2.
Added: Permission column to avatar list.
Added: Ability to double-click bindings to replace them.
Added: Window to replace binds, shows both old and new buttons.
Removed: Mode selection.
Fixed: Line Endings in llpanellogin.h.
Fixed: Texture load progressbar extending offscreen sometimes.
Fixed: Compile.
Fixed: Keybindings tab layout inconsistencies.
Fixed: Avatar turning around when resetting camera.
Fixed: Missing RLVa string when enabling/disabling RLVa.
Merge with Release.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.7.1
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="38"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Changed: Improved developer conversation auto-response message.
Changed: Version to 2.7.1.
Removed: Disabled Animation Manipulation floater for now.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.7.0
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="169"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added (WIP): Pose manipulation to 'Animation Manipulation' floater. Not functional yet.
Added: Human readable action names to keybinding lists.
Added (WIP): Ability to simple change/replace single keybinds. Not functional yet.
Changed: Renamed 'Move Forward/Backwards' (camera) to Zoom In/Out.
Changed: Keybinding column widths to fit everything in.
Changed: Relabeled 'Region' to 'Land Options' in german UI to match the english one.
Changed: Overhauled 'Script Information' floater layout.
Changed: Version to 2.7.0 - Decaying Dragon.
Fixed: Line Endings in llpanellogin.cpp.
Fixed: Login button being greyed out for firt timers since LL code merge.
Fixed: Line Endings in llfloaterpreferences.cpp.
Fixed: Special keys like Enter not immediately registering after ticking any mask checkbox.
Removed: UUID line editor and 'Create' button from the 'Animation Manipulation' floater.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.6.9
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="363"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Show an automated message whenever someone not in my friendlist opens a conversation with me.
Added: Missing optional XML parameters to panel.xml.
Added: Ability to flag scrolllist entries for easy removal later.
Added: New floater that allows manipulation of animations around you including your own avatar.
- Allows temporarily saving animations into a list for playing them on avatars.
- Allows creating/adding new animations to the list from a UUID.
- Allows removing entries from the list to get rid of unwanted animations.
- Allows viewing general information about saved animations such as their duration and if they loop.
- Allows playing anyone's animations including your own, at any speed you want, including backwards.
- Allows freezing avatar animations.
- Allows stopping all animations.
- Allows restarting currently playing animations, useful for synchronizing dances.
Added: Option to disable other people's attached lights without removing your own.
Added: Option to disable projector images being reflected in shiny surfaces.
Added: Option for projector images to 'Display' tab for easy toggling.
Changed: Made getting the my UUID a global centralized function of gAgent.
Changed: Allow global time factor being altered all the way down to pause via menu.
Changed: Layout of 'Uploads' tab to match all others.
Changed: Version to 2.6.9.
Fixed: Borderless Window Mode being greyed out if for some reason the defunct FullScreen debug was still enabled.
Fixed: Wrong layout panel name for local chat 'Chat History' button.
Fixed: Missing separators in some keybinding action menus.
Fixed: About Viewer floater throwing XML warnings.
Fixed: Focus point not resetting when zooming on something or someone and changing to a different camera preset.
Fixed: Default Upload Folder tab not appearing in preferences.
Fixed: 'Browser' tab's layout not exactly matching that of all others.
Removed: All languages except german and english.
Misc: Removal of unused code.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.6.8
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="51"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Changed: Version to 2.6.8.
Fixed: Compile.
Fixed: 'Dragon' main menu being broken after merge.
Merge with Release.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.6.7
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="247"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Camera Field of View option to machinima sidebar.
Added: Ability to add infinite additional and/or alternative bindings for everything.
Added: Ability to select one or more keybinds and delete them with a single click.
Added: Some additional bindings to most modes that were missing.
Changed: Preferences "Display" tab bottombar layout.
Changed: Preferences floater layout slightly to look cleaner.
Changed: Internal Browser space between content and the edge of the floater.
Changed: Make enabling Deferred force all necessary code and features to on.
Changed: Completely overhauled the preferences 'Keybindings' tab.
Changed: Fixed keybinding buttons and displays into lists.
Changed: Wording on the loadingscreen tip when an update is downloading.
Changed: Some display tab options to enable with Deferred instead of pre-deferred shader options.
Changed: Show the invite to session button in IM tabs only if the session is P2P or a ad-hoc conference.
Changed: Output the modifier keys in 'Keybindings' tab as easily understandable strings.
Changed: 'Display' tab bottom padding for preset buttons to match those in the 'Keybinding' tab.
Changed: Version to 2.6.7.
Fixed: Color for self on minimap.
Removed: Export button because we export (save) everything immediately anyway.
Misc: Cleaned up some preferences code, improved performance when preferences is open slightly.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.6.6
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="429"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Toolbar button styled combobox buttons for login and elsewhere.
Added: Projector Shadow Resolution sliders to Sidebar.
Added: Chat History button to IM tab toolbar.
Added: Missing chat history icon texture.
Changed: Moved Inventory Library option from Viewer tab to UI tab.
Changed: Moved Show Inbox/Outbox option from Viewer tab to UI tab.
Changed: UI tab "Misc" section layout, segmented it with a separator.
Changed: Moved SLURL Teleport in Chat to Chat tab.
Changed: Overhauled the internal webbrowser layout.
Changed: Replaced the normal combobox button images with the new toolbar ones in login.
Changed: Default value for tooltip alive time while mouse is away to 0.1, making it a lot snappier.
Changed: Make Sidebar only refresh the controls on toggle, should improve performance drastically while its opened.
Changed: Revamped the vector control code, unified into one function for each of the 4 maximum values (X Y Z W).
Changed: Glow Max Alpha slider decimal digits down to 3 since we controlled it in 0.001 steps anyway.
Changed: Moved Motion Blur further to the top.
Changed: Organized multiple option types into smaller slider groups just like in preferences.
Changed: Overhauled texture picker layout. Vertical approach.
Changed: Pipette icon. Need to do a new one.
Changed: Statusbar media, draw distance and preset icon layout.
Changed: Loginscreen location combo width to match the other widgets.
Changed: Moved IM tab voice indicator a bit for better spacing.
Changed: Overhauled open object floater.
Changed: Version to 2.6.6.
Fixed: Pressing Cancel on the System UI notification opens preferences.
Fixed: Made the URL in the internal webbrowser readable.
Fixed: Shadow Projector sliders not properly syncing.
Fixed: Texture resolution not showing ontop of texture.
Fixed: Warnings in floater_texture_ctrl.xml caused by remnants from Nirans Viewer.
Removed: Unused shadow projector Resolution Multiplicator option.
Removed: Camera options from Machinima Sidebar.
Misc: Cleanup.
Misc: Pulled MAINT-7156 on Oz's suggestion.
MAINT-7156: do not use the server-supplied agent email when sending a postcard because it is obfuscated and not needed
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.6.5
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="259"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Extra Vector2 support, not as complete as Vector4 but everything needed for upcoming changes.
Added: Ability to control each projector's shadow resolution.
Added: Ability to ignore the System UI Scale change notification.
Changed: Use a Vector2 for projector shadow resolution.
Changed: Shadow allocation code to be faster and fix an issue with shadows staying when disabling them.
Changed: Inverted the System UI Scale notification answers to prevent it from opening preferences by default when ignoring it.
Changed: Use the developer always-on styled avatarlistitem only if i'm not in the friendlist, respect online status.
Changed: Replaced the Viewer icon on my developer entry with a "DEVELOPER" label.
Changed: Inverted the Moderator and Developer tag colors. Blue seems better for the Developer tag.
Changed: Don't allow Glow Width below 0.1, 0 would disable it.
Changed: Current Outfit scroll panel layout to match the other tabs.
Changed: Ignore NearMeRange debug for any radar like list and use a fixed 4800m range instead.
Changed: Version to 2.6.5.
Fixed: (POTENTIAL) Blue badge loadingscreen tip cutting off for unknown reasons.
Fixed: Login to anything other than "Last Location" doesn't work.
Fixed: German title for the quick presets floater cutting off.
Fixed: More artifacts in german main menu.
Misc: Updated most of the login panels internal code.
Misc: pipeline.cpp code fixup that got broken on revert.
Backed out changeset: 3abfd5d5c5c4 ~ having another stab at this.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.6.4
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="221"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Show me as fake, temporary, permission-less friendlist entry in case the user doesn't have me in his friendlist to make contacting me easy.
Added: Use a special background and show a Viewer badge with tooltip on my friendlist entry to show that i'm the developer.
Changed: Made Tone Mapping and Color Correction default.
Changed: Left Shoulder and Right Shoulder camera preset look height angle.
Changed: Commented out some save snapshot code on Viewer cleanup. Unused.
Changed: Enable projector shadow toggle only if the light is a projector.
Changed: Don't show ourselves in the nearby avatar list.
Changed: Sorting to sort me (the developer) always at the top.
Changed: People panel nearby, friendlist, group, blocked and recent layouts to fix a huge bunch of minor icon clippings.
Changed: Blocked object icon size to prevent it from appearing washed out due to being scaled bigger than the texture size.
Changed: Show permission code, made it fire the entire block only if necessary.
Changed: Moderator/Developer chat tag code, compacted it.
Fixed: Several snapshot text boxes using hardly readable text colors.
Fixed: IM Chat line editor too high with multi-line disabled after fix for multi-line.
Fixed: German translation for the "Set Cache" button.
Fixed: Group icons being slightly cut off on the right in group chat toasts.
Misc: Code cleanup for commit f7e81eabbdcac58b6c8617d7749437c3200231b4 pointed out by Cinder.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.6.3
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="130"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Huge UI size option for 4k display resolution.
Added: Option to toggle Environment Map on shiny surfaces in Deferred Rendering.
Changed: Made the blue badge loadingscreen tip a bit more clear.
Changed: Animation time and type for opening/closing the display tabs in preferences.
Changed: Allow webpages to be scaled with UI size again. Ugh.
Changed: Version to 2.6.3.
Fixed: Sunlight reflections are missing with SSR on. Thanks to Cynder Starfall for making me look into it.
Fixed: Gestures can't be deactivated via inventory right click menu entry "deactivate".
Fixed: IM/Groupchat chatbar doing weird stuff and bugging out with multiline enabled.
Misc: Cleanup.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.6.2
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="313"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Checkbox to control weither a projector should cast a shadow or not. (LOCAL)
Added: Distance display to "Nearby" people panel.
Added: Loadingscreen tip for the Email verification.
Added: Cinematic Camera option to camera preferences tab.
Added: Scene Memory info to about floater.
Changed: Properly carry over the shader success signal when toggling shaders.
Changed: Improved SSAO defaults even further.
Changed: Improved some loadingscreen tips.
Changed: Improved scaling of text field widgets, fixes slider text fields having a slightly darker color at the bottom.
Changed: Improved SSR looks a bit.
Changed: Object Quality "Very High" to 7.5 and "Ultra" to 10.
Changed: Inventory filter being to big.
Changed: Version to 2.6.2.
Fixed: Warnings in panel_places.xml.
Fixed: Compile.
Fixed: Floater Script Limits floater warnings and new size.
Fixed: German translation for the cycle link/face menu entries.
Fixed: Inventory inbox background not big enough.
Fixed: German translation in about floater containing weird symbols.
Fixed: Inventory inbox layout clipping.
Removed: Non-functional Normalmap Scale option from preferences.
Removed: Unused Blocked List menu entry.
Misc: Cleanup.
Merge with Release. (215 changes)
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.6.1
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="285"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Ability to change the cloud noise texture in edit sky floater, without restart this time around.
Added: Cloud Noise Maps from Nirans Viewer, tweaked the High Resolution one to be smaller.
Added: Loadingscreen tip system.
Added: 22 completely new tips, shorter and more helpful than before.
Added: Another cloud noise map.
Added: Downloading Update loadingscreen text. (Untested)
Changed: Most if not all notifications links about downloads and viewer versions to my own links.
Changed: Tweaks to SSAO smoothing.
Changed: Tweaked IM floater chat bar positioning and size, long overdue.
Changed: Loadingscreen layout.
Changed: Initial startup loading percentages.
Changed: Increased wearables wait timeout to lessen cases in which you are falsely presented with the choose sex dialog.
Changed: Allow parsing icons in chat, history and picks again.
Changed: Version to 2.6.1
Changed: Disabled showing Release Notes on first start on a new version.
Fixed: Shadows on certain material surfaces getting stuck when quick-toggling shadows.
Fixed: Several XUI warnings in a bunch of floaters.
Fixed: Warning about top toolbar tooltip missing.
Fixed: Bad middle segment toolbar button scaling.
Fixed: SSR Resolution slider duplicate in preferences - display.
Fixed: Release Notes popup link after update.
Removed: HTTP Inventory option from Preferences.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.6
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="206"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Manually added RLVa back into the Viewer. Might need fixing.
Added: All necessary RLVa debugs.
Changed: Replaced llmin(llmax()) with the much simpler llclamp.
Changed: LLZoomer to set the zoom to 0.9 of the current value instead of dividing 1 by 1.1.
Changed: Massive Overhaul to the flycam code.
Changed: Clamped camera movement more reliable with extreme variable framerates.
Changed: Xbox360 Controller defaults a bit to match the new altered movement speed.
Changed: Enabled RLVa tab in Preferences.
Changed: Enabled RLVa submenu in Dragon main menu.
Changed: Version to 2.6.
Fixed: Stand/Stop/Flying button not clickable.
Fixes: Camera preset sliders not refreshing when pressing default.
Fixed: Zoom not taking effect immediately when smoothing is still active from previous smoothed zoom movement.
Fixed: Lineendings.
Fixed: RLVa, Compile.
Merge with RLVa.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.5.6
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="257"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Option to toggle Motion Blur between "Everything" , "My Avatar &amp; Objects" , "Objects Only".
Added: Option to control Screen Space Reflection's brightness.
Added: Selective De-Fullbright menu option, per feedback.
Changed: Unlocked already prepared SSR Brightness option in Machinima Sidebar.
Changed: Massive overhaul of the "Edit Shape" panel. Breaking all other edit wearables, they need fixing too.
Changed: Removed 3D previews of shape edit.
Changed: Made shape edit sliders much smaller and use less extra gap pixels between them.
Changed: Snapshot floater "Refresh" button label to "NEW SNAP" for when we translate it.
Changed: More Edit Wearables layout changes and layout consistency fixes.
Changed: Made some consistency changes to COF wearables panel to fit in with the other recent changes.
Changed: Version to 2.5.6
Fixed: Impostors being included in Motion Blur rendering.
Fixed (Workaround): Region Water flickering when its near the far clip plane with enabled Object Object Occlusion.
Fixed: Stand button clipping outside the Movement floater.
Fixed: Warns in floater_moveview.xml.
Fixed: Warns in panel_outfit_gallery.xml.
Fixed: Conversations button flashing forever.
Fixed: Alt keybinds having their mask and key strings on the wrong size creating weird labels.
Fixed: Newly introduced temp attachments tab broke the layout in Appearance - Outfits.
Merge with Bento RC
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.5.5
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="389"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Changed: Stop cloud and water ripple movement while freezing the world.
Changed: Made sure Deferred shaders can only be toggled with Deferred enabled.
Changed: Made sure shadow maps can only be quick-allocated with Deferred enabled.
Changed: Make fast-toggling shaders return a proper value in case we ever want to use it for something.
Changed: Disallow setting any memory higher than 1992 or lower than 128 to prevent memory issues.
Changed: Limit the memory slider min value to 128mb and the max to 1992 in case the code doesn't do it.
Changed: Open the Appearance floater with the "My Outfits" tab instead of the "Outfit Gallery".
Changed: Moved chat tags into the avatar name cache call, should fix a rare case if tags being reverted/missing.
Changed: Use the GLManager's VRAM as max and include SL's usage into the memory calculations when not using a NVidia Card.
Changed: Disable Object Object Occlusion by default. (We might want to enable this in case of AMD Card)
Changed: Disable Spellcheck by default.
Changed: Version to 2.5.5
Fixed: Self-inflicted issue that broke toasting when local chat is in Convo floater and Convo floater is closed.
Fixed: (QUICKFIX) Sidebar vanishing when toggled off instead of sliding out.
Fixed: Toggling Godrays with Deferred disabled causes the Viewer to crash.
Fixed: Toggling SSR with Deferred disabled causes the Viewer to crash.
Fixed: Toggling Blur Light with Deferred disabled causes the Viewer to crash.
Fixed: Toggling SSAO with Deferred disabled causes the Viewer to crash.
Fixed: Toggling Shadows with Deferred disabled causes the Viewer to crash.
Fixed: Changing shadow resolution caused the shadow detail option to revert to its previous value.
Fixed: Only refresh and draw the Machinima Sidebar when its really visible but respect the slide animation.
Misc: Machinima Sidebar code cleanup.
Misc: Code Cleanup. Line Endings.
Misc: Make resetDeferredShaders() return a value so we can use it as boolean.
Misc: Made toggling shadows return a proper value in case we ever want to use it for something.
Misc: Massive preferences XML file cleanups.
Misc: Cleanup in sidebar XML files.
Misc: Slight code cleanup in llimview and llviewercontrol.
Misc: Cleanup some debugging code in llfloaterpreferences.
Merge with Bento
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.5.4
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="90"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Shadow Resolution sliders to Machinima Sidebar.
Added: Screen Space Reflection Brightness slider to Machinima Sidebar. (Coming Soon)
Changed: Make progress panel background only appear when logging in.
Changed: Made Machinima Sidebar able to utilize coded functions.
Changed: Made Machinima Sidebar use the vector4 and vector3 functions to allow changing them properly.
Changed: Version to 2.5.4.
Misc: Line Endings and Code Cleanup.
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.5.3
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="220"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: VRAM usage display to preferences.
Added: Changelog text block for 2.5.3. Template changes, need to fill in later.
Changed: Camera smoothness to it's intended default value.
Changed: Custom System Memory to be the default, force 128mb by default in code.
Changed: Texture console VRAM display, show colored segments to indicate what's taken by SL and what isn't.
Changed: Texture console memory display, renamed bars to Scene and System to match preferences.
Changed: Replaced the progress bar textures with more fitting ones.
Changed: Made Progress Screen transparent, changed it's layout for the new progressbar texture.
Changed: Moved OpenGL 3.0 Texture Compression option to top.
Changed: Made System and Scene Memory slider change max value depending on the available memory.
Changed: Default value of Scene Memory Debug to 256mb.
Changed: Made labeling for System Memory and GPU Memory Usage more clear.
Changed: Version to 2.5.3.
Fixed: Compile
Removed: Custom System Memory option.
Removed: Custom System Memory option from preferences.
Merge with Bento
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.5.2
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="25"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Changed: Version to 2.5.2.
Merge with Linden VLC Release
              </text>
              <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top_pad="10"
    width="250"/>
              <text
              follows="top|left|right"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="14"
              top_delta="-6"
              left_pad="3"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="false"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
2.5.1
              </text>
              <text
              follows="top|left"
              font="SansSerifSmall"
              font_shadow="soft"
              halign="left"
              height="480"
              top_pad="3"
              left="7"
              name="changelog_text"
              bg_visible="true"
              bg_writeable_color="Black_50" 
              width="990"
              word_wrap="false">
Added: Pie Menu popup animation speed option to ui preferences.
Added: Chat history name background tagging for Mod + Dev and Developer only.
Changed: Pie Menu popup animation look.
Changed: Made alpha/dealpha able to alpha/dealpha single faces and multiple selected faces from different objects.
Changed: SSAO defaults, slightly less strong when multiple corners are close together.
Changed: Version to 2.5.1.
Changed: Login panel layout, added toggleable changelog.
Misc: Code tagging.
              </text>
       </panel>
       </scroll_container>
      </layout_panel>
  </layout_stack>
  
  <panel
  follows="right|left|bottom"
  height="150"
  layout="topleft"
  left="0"
  name="panel_login2"
  focus_root="true" 
  bottom="-1"
  width="996">
    <layout_stack
    border_size="0"
    follows="all"
    height="150"
    layout="topleft"
    left="0"
    mouse_opaque="true"
    name="root_stack"
    orientation="horizontal"
    top="0"
    width="996">
      <layout_panel
      auto_resize="true"
      follows="all"
      height="120"
      layout="topleft"
      mouse_opaque="true"
      name="info_panel"
      top_pad="0"
      width="200">
       <button
       follows="left|top"
       height="18"
       control_name="ShowChangelogs"
       is_toggle="true"
       image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
        image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
       label="Changelogs"
       font="SansSerif"
       font.style="BOLD"
       layout="topleft"
       left="1"
       halign="center"
       name="version_info_link"
       top="17"
       width="120"/>
       <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left|right"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left_pad="1"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top="25"
    width="78"/>
      </layout_panel>
      <layout_panel
      auto_resize="false"
      follows="all"
      height="130"
      layout="topleft"
      mouse_opaque="true"
      name="root_panel"
      top_pad="0"
      width="395">
       
       <text
        follows="left|top|right"
        font="SansSerifBig"
        font_shadow="soft"
        font.style="BOLD"
        halign="center"
        height="20"
        top="0"
        left="0"
        name="app_name_text"
        width="380"
        word_wrap="true">
[APP_NAME]
        </text>
       
       <button
        follows="left|top"
        height="18"
        control_name="PreferencesLogin"
        image_overlay_alignment="left"
        pad_bottom="0"
        image_overlay="Command_Preferences_Icon"
        image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
        image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
        label="Preferences"
        is_toggle="false"
        font="SansSerif"
        font.style="BOLD"
        label_color="1 1 1 0.7"
        layout="topleft"
        left="1"
        halign="center"
        name="pref_btn"
        top="17"
        width="122">
              <button.commit_callback
              function="Floater.Toggle"
              parameter="preferences"/>
        </button>
        <!--<button
        follows="right|top"
        height="18"
        image_overlay_alignment="left"
        image_bottom_pad="1"
        pad_bottom="0"
        image_overlay="Command_Profile_Icon"
        image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
        image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
        label="Sign Up"
        font="SansSerif"
        font.style="BOLD"
        label_color="1 1 1 0.7"
        layout="topleft"
        left_pad="1"
        halign="center"
        name="create_new_account_text"
        top_delta="0"
        width="100"/>-->
        <!--<button
        follows="right|top"
        height="18"
        image_unselected="transparentj2c"
        image_selected="transparentj2c"
        label="Forgot Login details?"
        font="SansSerifBig"
        font.style="BOLD"
        label_color="1 1 1 0.7"
        layout="topleft"
        left="0"
        halign="right"
        name="forgot_password_text"
        top_pad="0"
        width="100"/>-->
        <button
        follows="right|top"
        height="18"
        image_overlay_alignment="left"
        pad_bottom="0"
        image_overlay="Command_AboutLand_Icon"
        image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
        image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
        label="Grid Status"
        font="SansSerif"
        font.style="BOLD"
        label_color="1 1 1 0.7"
        layout="topleft"
        left_pad="1"
        halign="center"
        name="grid_btn"
        top_delta="0"
        width="111">
        <button.commit_callback
          function="PromptShowURL"
          parameter="WebLaunchExternalTarget,http://status.secondlifegrid.net/"/>
        </button>
        <combo_box
        allow_text_entry="true"
        follows="left|top"
        height="18"
        max_chars="256"
        layout="topleft"
        label="Select a Grid"
        top_delta="0"
        left_pad="1"
        name="server_combo"
        width="157"
        visible="true">
          <combo_box.combo_editor
          font="SansSerif"
          font.style="BOLD"
          font_shadow="soft"
          text_tentative_color="0.7 0.7 0.7 0.7"
          cursor_color="White"
          text_color="0.75 0.75 0.75 0.7"
          background_image="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
          background_image_disabled="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
          background_image_focused="Toolbar_Middle_Off"/>
          <combo_box.combo_button
          scale_image="true"
          image_overlay="R"
          image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Dropdown_Off"
          image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Dropdown_Selected"
          image_disabled="Toolbar_Middle_Dropdown_Off" />
            <combo_box.combo_list
              bg_writeable_color="White_02"
              background_visible="true"/>
        </combo_box>
        <line_editor
        commit_on_focus_lost="false"
        follows="left|top"
        height="22"
        label="Username"
        left="113"
        tool_tip="The username you chose when you registered, like bobsmith12 or Steller Sunshine"
        top_pad="12"
        name="username_combo"
        width="152"/>
        <line_editor
        follows="left|top"
        commit_on_focus_lost="false"
        height="22"
        max_length_bytes="16"
        name="password_edit"
        label="Password"
        is_password="true" 
        select_on_focus="true"
        left_delta="0"
        top_pad="3"
        width="152" />
        <check_box
        control_name="RememberPassword"
        follows="left|top"
        font="SansSerifSmall"
        height="18"
        left_pad="0"
        label="remember"
        top_delta="2"
        name="remember_check"
        width="200"/>
        <combo_box
        allow_text_entry="true"
        control_name="NextLoginLocation"
        follows="left|top"
        height="23"
        max_chars="128"
        top_pad="5"
        left="113"
        name="start_location_combo"
        width="160">
          <combo_box.combo_editor
          background_image="TextField_Off"
          background_image_disabled="TextField_Disabled"
          background_image_focused="TextField_Active"/>
          <combo_box.item
          label="My last location"
          name="MyLastLocation"
          value="last" />
          <combo_box.item
          label="My home"
          name="MyHome"
          value="home" />
          <combo_box.combo_button
          image_unselected="ComboToolbarButton_Off"
          image_selected="ComboToolbarButton_Selected"
          image_pressed="ComboToolbarButton_Selected" 
          image_pressed_selected="ComboToolbarButton_Selected"/>
          <combo_box.drop_down_button
          image_unselected="ComboToolbarButton_Off"
          image_selected="ComboToolbarButton_Selected"
          image_pressed="ComboToolbarButton_Selected" 
          image_pressed_selected="ComboToolbarButton_Selected"
          image_disabled="ComboToolbarButton_Disabled"/>
        </combo_box>
       <button
       follows="left|top"
       height="23"
       image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
       image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
       label="*BREATHE FIRE*"
       font="SansSerif"
       font.style="BOLDITALIC"
       label_color="1 1 1 0.8"
       layout="topleft"
       left="113"
       name="connect_btn"
       top_pad="3"
       width="152"/>
      </layout_panel>
      <layout_panel
      auto_resize="true"
      follows="all"
      height="100"
      layout="topleft"
      mouse_opaque="true"
      name="help_panel"
      top_pad="0"
      width="200">
       <view_border
    bevel_style="in"
    follows="top|left|right"
    height="1"
    layout="topleft"
    left="0"
    name="cost_text_border"
    top="25"
    width="120"/>
       <button
        follows="right|top"
        height="18"
        image_unselected="Toolbar_Middle_Off"
        image_selected="Toolbar_Middle_Selected"
        label="Quit"
        font="SansSerif"
        font.style="BOLD"
        label_color="1 1 1 0.7"
        layout="topleft"
        left_pad="1"
        halign="center"
        name="quit_btn"
        top_delta="-8"
        width="77"/>
      </layout_panel>
    </layout_stack>
  </panel>
</panel>
